<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Dr. Hope</string>

    <string name="title_activity_full_screen_score_card">FullScreenScoreCardActivity</string>
    <string name="dummy_button">Dummy Button</string>
    <string name="dummy_content">DUMMY\nCONTENT</string>
    <string name="girl_intro">Hey my name is Kiara. I am 14 years old. Everybody teases me by calling me tiara but I think I have a nice name. I like to dance a lot. I keep dancing always. Mumma says I should take rest also but I want to become the best dancer when I grow up. I also like to run a lot. My teacher says I am the fastest in my class. Beating boys is fun, they get very angry when they loose from a girl. I like pink color a lot. I have a pink bag and shoes, my favorite. Its now 7am in the morning and it is time for me to go to school. And my mom is calling me. So, yeah. See you!</string>
    <string name="boy_intro">Hey I am Raj. I am 14 years old. I like to swim and play basketball. I am very tall in my class and everybody loves to have me in their team. I also like to play Table tennis. My mumma makes me eat lots of veggies, but I do not like them. She says they are important since I like to play so much and I am growing up. My favorite color is black and I always like to wear it. Its now 7am in the morning and it is time for me to go to school. And my mom is calling me. So, yeah. See you!</string>
    <string name="if_user_says_no">Thank you for your time and we hope you learnt about how lives can be saved by donating organs.</string>
    <string name="if_user_says_yes">Dr. Hope is a small initiative by IgiftLife Foundation to spread awareness on Organ Donation.</string>
    <string name="go_to_school">I don\'t feel very well though. Should I go to school or not?</string>
    <string name="hello">Hello</string>
    <string name="who_would_you_like_to_meet">Who would you like to meet?</string>
    <string name="kiara">Kiara</string>
    <string name="raj">Raj</string>
    <string name="dr_hope_is_a_small_initiative_by_igiftlife_foundation_to_spread_awareness_on_organ_donation">Dr. Hope is a small initiative by IgiftLife Foundation to spread awareness on Organ Donation.</string>
    <string name="yes">YES</string>
    <string name="no">NO</string>
    <string name="touch_anywhere_on_the_screen_to_continue">Touch Anywhere on the Screen to Continue</string>
    <string name="pledge_today">Pledge today</string>
    <string name="play_again">PLAY AGAIN</string>
    <string name="dr_hope">Dr. Hope</string>
    <string name="_0">0</string>
    <string name="_3">3</string>
    <string name="next"><![CDATA[Next >>]]></string>
    <string name="your_score">Your Score!</string>
    <string name="_60">60</string>
    <string name="well_tried">Well Tried!</string>
    <string name="try_again">TRY AGAIN?</string>
    <string name="visit_igiftlife_com_to_learn_about_organ_donation">Visit IgiftLife.com to learn about organ donation</string>
    <string name="not_feeling_well">I don\'t feel very well though. Do you think I should go to school?</string>

</resources>
